w3catalog.com 2019-05-07

# W3 Catalog Web Directory - Privacy Policy

W3 Catalog respects your right to the privacy of your personal information you provide us on our web site. To that end, any personal information you provide to W3 Catalog will be known only to two parties: you and W3 Catalog. The following policy is intended to explain how your personal information will be treated as you make use of our site and its features. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.

**Submission**

During the W3 Catalog Submission, we require information from the user on our submit form. A user must provide contact information (such as name amd email). We use this information to contact the user about services on our site for which he has expressed interest.

**Traffic Data**

Each time a visitor comes to W3 Catalog, our server - like most on the Web - collects some basic technical information, including, for example, your domain name,  referral data, and browser and platform type.

We also count, track and aggregate the visitor's activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at our site (e.g., tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the site, etc.). To these ends, we may merge information about visitors and visits into group data; but we will not disclose your individual identity or personally identifiable data.

**Special Offers**

Established members will occasionally receive information on new services, offers or special deals. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications.

**Data Removal**

If you would like to unsubscribe from an W3 Catalog e-mail list, please follow the instructions at the bottom of the e-mail itself.

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

W3 Catalog will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information without your consent except as requested by government or law enforcement authorities.

**Sites**

W3 Catalog contains many links to other sites on the web. We cannot control and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other Web sites.

If you have any further questions or concerns about our privacy policies and use of personal information, please contact us.
